Look, I took an insurance policy of Rs 11230 with the new bike
which was
valid for five years, still after one year I had to
take an insurance policy of Rs 6565.
Hello friends, welcome to my channel Tech
Hindi friends, if you are going to buy any new bike,
scooter or any other tool
or you have to buy any vehicle some time back, then
next I am going to tell you
some very important things related to * Miller's insulin, about
which
you should have correct and complete information,
otherwise
you may lose thousands of rupees due to lack of information.
Friends, some time ago the
Insurance Regulatory and Development
Authority of India made changes
in the rules of the two-wheeler insurance policy, it was
made a rule that you must take a
five-year insurance policy with the new two-wheeler,
and this is happening now,
you are taking it and have been taking it since some time, right now there is a
500-rupee policy,
many doctors are very worried about it,
why are there many doctors on this,
after which people are worshipped and
Lack of correct information can lead to losses,
so further I am going to tell you all the points
regarding the insurance policy of Stop Panchal,
in the beginning I will start with the basics, then I will
tell you about it at the advanced level, although
many people will know about the basic things,
still it is important to tell you in advance so that today's
topic can be completely clear, the
parcel insurance that you are
getting with Tubelight is basically
available in two parts, the first part is
for the first year and the
insurance policy of the first year is the Body
NTP Insurance Policy, that is, in the
third party insurance policy and
after one year of buying the vehicle, if you meet with an
accident, then what happens in it, that is,
any damage to your vehicle is
covered in the insurance policy
and if there is any damage to the third party due to you, any harm
to the animal, any
damage to the third party's vehicle or property, then that too is
covered in that insurance policy and as soon as one
year is over, then the next
Only the third party insurance
policy of TP is written for 14 years, that is the only one and
after completion of this, if you have an
accident, then no damage to your vehicle will be
covered in it, only
any damage to the property of each other's vehicle is
covered, this is a 5 year
student policy and to understand it better, let me
tell you here that
now see, I bought this last year
with this bike, I had
taken this insurance policy of Chief General Insurance,
which was only for five years and the
premium was Rs. 11200.25, you
see here, the policy is not for just one year, it was
from 1 February 2021 to 31 January
2022 and the third party
insurance policy is valid for five years i.e.
from 1 February 2021 to 31 January 2036,
after completion of the first one year, in the next four years, you
get two benefits, one is the third party's time and
place is covered, second is these  At the
traffic police catches you, if
you show your insurance policy here, then
you will not be charged any challan
for 5 years by the definition of insurance. So
friends, till here in the video, the basic
level information is complete,
now we are going to provide advanced level information,
and here total three points, if you liked it
till now then do
like the video and if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel then
please do subscribe to the channel. Let's
come to point number one, it is
completed at once, whatever other imbalance you have, it has expired
but you still have balance, so what can you do here, so
point number one is that
after completion of one year, you can take an insurance policy for the front and damage of
your bike, scooter, any two wheeler as per your wish
and
understand till here that it is not necessary that you
take the insurance policy of the same company which you had earlier, it is not necessary,
again you can take the pods for one year, two to three fruits,
as much as you are taking, Bua  Now you
can also take it from another company. For example,
I had initially insured my bike with
SBI General
Insurance. And the one I have taken now is
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance and the premium was Rs. 6565.
You can see that I have taken it for one year
from 1st February 2012 to 31st January
2030. So you should have two
companies. If you want to see them first, you can take it from another
company. If you get good
quality and good
response, then you can take it. So
here, point one is clear about the point above, it is
also important to know that if you have taken this policy from two
different companies, the first one is from a
different company and later on, it can be done in
case of accident.
Now
before telling this point, let me tell you some important things related to the car.
Now I would like to tell you
that if you have a car and you
want hundred percent Gemini level insurance for your work, then this can help you.
video.com voot.com
is an online spare parts expert and from here you can
easily order spare parts for cars of all foreign companies along with Indian companies. The
interface is very easy. You just have to enter the
company model airplane of your work.
After that you can easily search here according to your car model
so that you will get to see the
same catalogue here according to your car model. You will get
to see separate catalogues for every part of the car
like engine, transmission, steering and all the
other parts.
In that catalogue you will get to
see the footage of all the lessons of that moment. The
name of the lesson, lesson number, description of the lesson,
how much that lesson will cost, you
can see all this here. You can also check the
compatibility of each lesson with your work
and if the part is
suitable for your program then you
can easily order it. Here
you will also get to see the 10 day return policy. The
link to the official website of video.com is in this  I will give the description of the video,
so please
go to goodcom and from there
definitely order the spare part for your work,
let's point Mintu, let me take care of that, then
their protection gets activated and
your Zone Times is from some other company
and the third party insurance of the first 5 years is from
some other insurance
company, so there is no problem, if there is an accident, then
whatever damage you have, then
your current policy of this company will take care of that
work, your existing third
party is from whichever company, then
whatever damage is there of the third party will be taken over there, there is no
problem, if you have
two different insurance policies then
you are not going to have any problem, understand this thing
and many times people
fool the insurance companies, who fool the people that
no sir, your third
party is from someone else, if you take it from whichever side then there will be a
problem, you should
not fall into this foolishness and that is why what I did was that I
took my bike from some other company to give me the memorandum, so you can see,
I have also taken it myself, there is no issue, there is no
problem, point extra Raja, so
you  I would like to tell you that it is not necessary
that you have insured your bike from the same showroom, if you have
rented a house or scooter,
you should go there and get it insured again, this is
not a necessary thing,
I would like to tell you that it is your choice, if you
want you can go to the showroom and get it insured at all,
but if you want you can do it
sitting at home, there are many policies in the market, there are many
options, many websites and apps, it is
your choice, you can do it yourself,
for whichever insurance company you want, you can take whatever premium you
want, whether it is low or high, you can take it, I have found one for Rs.
6565,
I have got the physio depression in this bike, I got the
total off,
apart from this, I got the art i.e. returned
toe involved, so I got
more facilities, I paid more than this, it is your
choice, if you want you can take the one with lesser permit, as you
feel right, so friends, this is a
5 year insurance policy, regarding which
many people still have doubts, in MS
Word this video your maximum dot is
more dot  It must have become clear, if you
liked the speed then do like and
share the video after the video and do tell
me your opinion by commenting,
apart from this if you have not subscribed to the channel
yet then
please subscribe to the channel and
also press the bell icon so that
you keep getting notifications of upcoming important videos, you get
60 English videos in the video, goodbye